virginwines.co.uk 2013-09-09

# Privacy policy | Help | Virgin Wines

Virgin Wines Online Limited ("Virgin Wines") is totally committed to protecting the privacy of our site visitors and customers and to promoting the responsible consumption of alcohol. The Virgin Wines team members are customers themselves of other Internet sites and fully appreciate and respect the importance of privacy on the Internet. We will not disclose information about our customers to third parties except where it is part of providing a service to you - e.g. arranging for a product to be sent to you, carrying out credit and other security checks and for the purposes of customer research and profiling or where we have your express permission to do so.

If you have any questions regarding our privacy policy, please email us at [privacy@virginwines.co.uk](mailto:privacy@virginwines.co.uk) or call 0843 224 1001.

## Your Consent

We will not sell, or make available, your name, address, e-mail address, credit card information or personal information to any third party (excluding partners from whom you may have linked to our site) without your permission. 

## Communication & Marketing

If you have made a purchase, or registered on our site, we may update you on our latest products, news and special offers via e-mail, post & telephone. All Virgin Wines members have the option to opt-out of receiving marketing communications from us and/or selected third parties. If you do not wish to continue to receive marketing from us and/or selected third parties you should opt-out by visiting 'Your Communication Preferences' in 'Your Account' on the Virgin Wines website. You can access 'Your Account' once you register and login. Or click on the "unsubscribe" link in any marketing email communications which we send you.

## What are Cookies?

A cookie is a small information file that is sent to your computer and is stored on your hard drive. If you have registered with us then your computer will store an identifying cookie which will save you time each time you re-visit Virgin Wines, by remembering your personal details. You can change the settings on your browser to prevent cookies being stored on your computer without your explicit consent. To access your account details or place an order online you will still need to login.   
Find out more about our cookies here.

## Site Statistics

We may disclose aggregate, anonymised statistics about the number of visitors to this Website or number of purchases made as required by our investors. We use an independent measurement and research company to gather data regarding the visitors to this Website on our behalf using cookies and code which is embedded in the site. Both the cookies and the embedded code provide statistical information about visits to pages on the site, the duration of individual page view, paths taken by visitors through the site, data on visitors' screen settings and other general information. Virgin Wines uses and stores this type of information, as with that obtained from other cookies used on the site, to help it improve the services to its users. Further information regarding the way in which this information is obtained and used can be obtained by contacting us at [privacy@virginwines.co.uk](mailto:privacy@virginwines.co.uk). 

## Protecting your security

We may use personal information provided by you in order to conduct appropriate anti-fraud checks. Personal information that you provide may be disclosed to a credit reference or fraud prevention agency, which may keep a record of that information. This is done only to confirm your identity - a credit check is not performed and your credit rating is unaffected.

## Transfers of your Information

The information that we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored at, a destination outside the European Economic Area ("EEA"). It may also be processed by staff operating outside the EEA who work for Virgin Wines or one of our suppliers. Such processing may, for example, be required in order to fulfill your order, process your payment details or provide support services. 

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the Internet is not completely secure. We will do our best to protect your personal data, but cannot guarantee the security of data transmitted to our site; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access. 

## Disclosures of your information

We may disclose your personal information to any of our group of companies. We may also disclose your personal information to third parties: 

  * in the event that Virgin Wines sells or buys any business or assets; 
  * if Virgin Wines or substantially all of its assets are acquired by a third party, in which case personal data which we hold about our customers may be one of the transferred assets; or 
  * if we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our terms of; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of Virgin Wines, our customers, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organisations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

## Third party sites

Our site may contain links to and from the websites of our partner networks, advertisers and other third parties. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that they have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies. Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites. 

## Age verification

Virgin Wines is committed to being a responsible supplier of alcohol and encourages a responsible attitude to drinking. We may use personal information provided by you in order to conduct appropriate age verification checks. Personal information that you provide may be disclosed to an age verification agency, which may keep a record of that information. This is done only to confirm your age.

## Checking your Details

If you wish to verify the details you have submitted to Virgin Wines you may do so by contacting us via the e-mail address or address given below. Our security procedures mean that we may request proof of identity before we reveal information. This proof of identity will take the form of your e-mail address and password submitted upon registration. You must therefore keep this information safe as you will be responsible for any action which we take in response to a request from someone using your e-mail and password. We would strongly recommend that you do not use the browser's password memory function as that would permit other people using your terminal to access your personal information. 

## Contacting us

Virgin Wines Online Limited (at the address below) is the data controller for the purpose of the Data Protection Act 1998 (the Act). You have the right to access the information which Virgin Wines holds about you and your right of access can be exercised in accordance with the Act. Any access request may be subject to a fee of £10 to meet our costs in providing you with details of the information we hold about you.

We are always pleased to hear from our customers (even if it is a complaint!). We are always grateful for any time you spend providing us with the knowledge we need to ensure our customers are completely satisfied - we want you to return to the site and to recommend us to your friends and family. If you have any questions or feedback about this statement, or if you would like us to stop processing your information, please do not hesitate to contact a customer service member of the Virgin Wines team, who will be delighted to answer any questions you may have.

You can contact customer services via email at [privacy@virginwines.co.uk](mailto:privacy@virginwines.co.uk), call on 0843 224 1001 or write to us at:

Virgin Wine Online Limited  
St James' Mill  
Whitefriars  
Norwich  
Norfolk  
NR3 1TN  
UK
